Mahmoud Al Masri Al Shayyah



Mahmoud.Masri1996@gmail.com



+961 70/293986



linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-al-masri-al-shayyah



https://mahmoud-ms1996.github.io/Portfolio/

Summary

Hi, I'm Mahmoud Al Masri Al Shayyah. Junior Front-End Developer with 1 year of experience designing and building responsive web design in the Freelancers. Proficient with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, swiper.js. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved Code and Design.

Experience



Training C#

El Haceb

Dec 2021 - Jan 2022 (2 months)

Full-stack Developer

KE business Development consulting Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

Education



Lebanese International University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Nov 2017 - Aug 2021 Web developer

Saida Technical Institute

Technical Baccalaureate - BT3, Industrial Mechanical 2015 - 2016

Licenses & Certifications



Skills

Front-End Development • Web Design • Research • User Experience Design (UED) • Web Services • Bootstrap • HTML5 • PHP • MySQL • Back-End Web Development